PRAYER TIME
Father, we thank you! How great you are!
Give thanks to God, give thanks to Him.
The SCOAN Revival Prophetic Service
Give thanks to Him!
Father, we thank You. Son of David, we ask for Your mercy and favour.
Thank You, Lord, in Jesus Christ' name!
The SCOAN Revival Prophetic Service
Right now, give your heart - give your heart and let the Holy Spirit enter.
Your heart is the temple, your heart is the prayer room.
Right now, give your heart, release your heart!
Ask the Holy Spirit to come to your heart. Come to my heart, Oh Lord!
Come to my heart, Oh Lord!
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Every familiar Spirit!
Out!
Right now begin to command them out of your life!
The SCOAN Revival Prophetic Service
You evil spirit!
You familiar spirit!
We say to you - come out!
Out!
In the name of Jesus we say to you - come out!
Leave my people right now!
In the name of Jesus, leave my people!
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Every knee shall bow; every tongue shall confess that Jesus is Lord.
I say in the name of Jesus,
every contrary spirit here!
Out!
In the name of Jesus!
Every contrary spirit!
Out!
In the name of Jesus!
Every contrary spirit!
Out!
I say, come out!
The SCOAN Revival Prophetic Service
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Within and outside!
Come out!
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
The SCOAN Revival Prophetic Service
Spirit of water.
The mother brought him to me to take care of him.
I destroyed everything about him.
The mother passed away.
I took control of him.
I am the spirit of death.
I want to destroy her marriage, her career.
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Every familiar spirit!
Out!
The SCOAN Revival Prophetic Service
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Come out, in the name of Jesus!
Amen!
Out, in the name of Jesus!
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Fire!
I want to go!
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Right now, I command every familiar spirit in your life!
Out!
Open your lips and begin to command them out!
Command them out!
The SCOAN Revival Prophetic Service
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
The SCOAN Revival Prophetic Service
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Amen!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
I will destroy her.
I want to give her sickness.
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Amen!
The SCOAN Revival Prophetic Service
Very stupid! Who is she?
I am going to scatter everything. I am going to confuse the family.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Amen!
The SCOAN Revival Prophetic Service
Right now, anywhere you have the pain in your organs, in your system,
right now, begin to command that pain out!
Are you on the wheelchair?
Are you paralysed, unable to walk, deaf and dumb?
Anywhere you are, under the canopy.
Overflow Congregation
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Amen!
Walk, in the name of Jesus!
Regain strength, in the name of Jesus! Ability to walk, come!
Come!
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Amen!
Be fit, in the name of Jesus!
Be strong, in the name of Jesus!
Amen!
In every area of your organs - be strong!
Be fit, in the name of Jesus!
Amen!
Be strong, in the name of Jesus!
Walk, in the name of Jesus!
Walk!
Healed in Jesus' Name Outside Auditorium - No Longer Using Walking Aids
The SCOAN Revival Prophetic Service
Wherever you are - within, outside, at home, here in the church -
we command you to walk, in the name of Jesus!
Amen!
At the command of Jesus, Blind Bartimaeus regained his sight.
We command you to walk, in the name of Jesus!
Amen!
At the command of Jesus, Blind Bartimaeus regained his sight.
We command you to walk, in the name of Jesus!
Regain strength, in the name of Jesus!
Every dry bone shall rise again - rise!
Anywhere in your organ - we command that pain to go!
Amen!
Say go!
Go!
In the name of Jesus!
You pain, you affliction, you infirmity, we command you - go!
Out of my blood - go!
Out of my bones - go!
Out of my flesh - go!
Out of my fluids - go!
We command you to go!
Go!
Right now, begin to walk!
Begin to walk!
Walk without pain, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Amen!
Healed in Jesus' Name Outside Auditorium - No Longer Using Walking Aids
Rejoice!
Thank you!
Give thanks to God!
Hallelujah!
Stretch your hand and pray for your nation, your country.
Redeem your nation; ask for revival for your nation.
Father Lord Jesus, redeem our nations, in the name of Jesus!
Spirit of corruption, spirit of manipulation, in the name of Jesus, we command them out of your nation!
Spirit of idolatry in your nation, we command them out in the name of Jesus!
Misrule, misappropriation, we command them out in the name of Jesus!
Let there be peace!
Peace in the East, In the South, in the North, in the West, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Right now, begin to remember those countries that are trouble nations, trouble zones.
All over the world, there are some nations that are trouble zones.
Prayer!
Prayer for the Nations with Prophet T.B. Joshua in Jesus' Name
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Let there be peace, in Jesus Christ's name we pray!